Devin Lynch

5079 Calvin Ave., Tarzana, CA 91356

(818) 472-9786 djlynch17@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/devin-j-lynch Git: github.com/dlynch42 Portfolio Site: <u>Here</u>

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Bachelor's Degree in Economics, Minor in Business University of Colorado, Boulder Boulder, CO May 2021

Relevant Course Work

- Calculus 2: Differential Equations, Taylor & Maclauren Series, Power Series, Sequences
- Financial Econometrics: Multivariate Linear Prediction, Garch, ARIMA, Matlab
- Econometrics: Simple/Multiple Regression, Asymptotics, Binary Variables, Heteroskedasticity
- Statistics: Distributions, Expectation, Sampling, Confidence Intervals, Inference, Regression
- International Trade: Production Functions, Heckscher-Olin Model, Rybezynski Theorem, Stopler-Samuelson Theorem
- · Physics of Music: Bits, Oscillators, Various Waves

EXPERIENCE

College Financial Representative Internship

Northwestern Mutual

May 2021 to September 2021

- · Obtained FINRA Series 6 and Series 63 licenses
- Presented complex financial topics to clients
- · Cultivated new client relationships

Student Athlete (Football)

University of Colorado, Boulder August 2017 to January 2021

- · Walk-on inside linebacker
- Earned Distinctions: Iron Man, Academic Honor Roll (3 Semesters)

CUIFC Executive Vice President - Community Relations

Phi Delta Theta Colorado Alpha

December 2019 to December 2020

- Founding Father of Colorado Alpha Chapter
- CUIFC liaison to Panhellenic and Office of Strategic Relations
- Established media presence for newly founded IFC

ABOUT ME

Detail-oriented Economics graduate with 4 years of Division 1 college football experience and a track record of academic success. A proven and dependable leader of teams who excels in high pressure environments looking for professional and personal growth. Continuing to enhance my programming skills with formal classes and growing my portfolio.

SKILLS, PROFICIENCIES, & INTERESTS

- Python
- C, C#, C++
- · SQL, R
- HTML, CSS, Java/JavaScript
- · Data Structures, Algorithms
- AI/ML/DL, OpenCV
- · Xcode, Unity, Vuforia
- Microsoft Office Suite
- · Coachable, Adaptive, Disciplined, Gritty
- · Surfer, Reader, Musician, Lifter

VOLUNTEER WORK

Student Volunteer

Phi Delta Theta, CU Boulder Football January 2018 to May 2021

- Various community service and philanthropic activities
- Activities include, but not limited to, trash clean up, camp assistant, Pie-A-Phi, Phi Delta Theta Live Like Lou Foundation, and Greek Week

Youth Football Camp Manager

Chaminade College Prep.

Summer 2016

- Created camp program with assistance from teammates and no oversight from coaches
- Taught kids mental and physical fundamentals of football